

SUMMARY

Frontend Developer,

Develops mainly using React.js (with Hooks) and vanilla JavaScript with redux. Passionate about solving daily challenges, with experience in the latest web technologies.

Can build a full-scale web app from PSD to a live responsive page.

CONTACT ME

Phone: 054-4594273

Portfolio:

https://rotemyehiel.github.io/rotempatrakeev-portfolio/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rotem-patrakeev-143608163/

Email

rotem8y@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Baking Traveling

LANGUAGES

Hebrew- Native English- High level

ARMY SERVICE

2010-2012

Computers Corps Commander and instructor of encryption courses.

ROTEM PATRAKEEV

Frontend Developer

EDUCATION

Coding Academy (Mister bit bootcamp)

January 2020 - May 2020

Web development course (Full Stack)

Holon Institute of Technology (HIT)

2015-2019

<u>B.Sc. Technology Management</u> -Information Systems Management and Development.

EXPERIENCE

Karma shopping (startup company)- Frontend developer

2022-today

Developing and enhancing our main web application using React.js (Hooks) and vanilla JavaScript, with expertise in creating responsive designs using flexbox. Developed web extensions and website integrated into the main product.

YIT- Frontend developer

2021-2022

Build desktop and responsive web apps using React.js, TypeScript and vanilla JavaScript.

In addition, Responsible from end-to-end for a main product from development to deployment.

Adworks Ltd- Full stack developer

2020-2021

Build a Next, React, Node.js apps from scratch such as: ecommerce app, scrapping app (using Puppeteer) and chrome extension.

Marmanet- Data Coordinator

2019

Comparison and concentration of data.

N & J Industrial Food Machinery LTD

2015-2019

Responsibility for the company's website-

Editing HTML, and marketing the web using Google Ads and Google Analytics, making technical support and orders.

TECH SKILLS

Programing:

JavaScript (ES6), HTML5, CSS3, SASS, TypeScript, Server with Node.JS.

Frameworks:

Next, Vue, Express.

Data manage:

MongoDB, SQL Server.

Libraries:

React, Redux, Jest, JSDOM, Storybook, Bootstrap, Webpack, jQuery, Puppeteer, Ajax, Axios and Font awesome.